<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Makini Analytics</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Makini Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimates of the risks of mortality by age and sex in DRC</title>
      <link>/2020/01/04/estimates-of-the-risks-of-mortality-by-age-and-sex-in-drc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/01/04/estimates-of-the-risks-of-mortality-by-age-and-sex-in-drc/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionCivil registration and vital statistics (CRVS) systems are essential for a variety of purposes, including for understanding the growth dynamics of the population concerned; assessment of the human aspects of socioeconomic development; and measurement, for insurance and social security purposes, of the risks of dying for males and females at specific ages.
Following the announcement, in March 2019, by the insurance market regulatory institution in the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC), of the granting of accreditations and authorizations to a first wave of private companies, there will be increasing demand for this kind of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Pacifique Mugaruka Ntabaza.
My interests lie where technology, development and data meet. I enjoy communicating with data on topical issues around poverty, vulnerability, crisis and financing for development.
This blog provides a platform for evidence to be shared to assist those advocating for a prosperous Democratic Republic of Congo in particular and Africa in general. The focus is on using evidence and data to bolster the case being made to politicians, development actors, businesses and society as a whole to be doing more to address the challenge of poverty and inequality.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>